<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en" xml:base="https://blog.vilijur.fish">
    <title>blog.vilijur.fish</title>
    <subtitle>a small pond in the internet sea</subtitle>
    <link href="https://blog.vilijur.fish/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://blog.vilijur.fish" />
    <updated>2026-02-01T12:13:57.258Z</updated>
    <id>https://blog.vilijur.fish</id>
    <author>
        <name>vilijur</name>
    </author>
    
        
        <entry>
            <title>About blog.vilijur.fish</title>
            <link href="https://blog.vilijur.fish/blog.vilijur.fish/posts/welcome/" />
            <id>https://blog.vilijur.fish/blog.vilijur.fish/posts/welcome/</id>
            <updated>2026-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
            <summary>a small pond in the internet sea</summary>
            <content type="html">
				&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my little corner of the Internet. As of writing this, there&#39;s not much here, though hopefully that changes soon. But what exactly can you find here?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wonder that too...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;site-navigation&quot;&gt;Site Navigation&lt;a data-pagefind-ignore href=&quot;#site-navigation&quot; class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; aria-label=&quot;Permalink to Site Navigation&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;tooltip&quot;&gt;Permanent link&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might find it good to know a few things about this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can&#39;t use the Post and Tags button in the menu on your browser for whatever reason, you can go &lt;a href=&quot;/tags/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to navigate the tags manually, and &lt;a href=&quot;/tags/posts/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to see all posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is also the &lt;a href=&quot;/extra/&quot;&gt;Extra&lt;/a&gt; page with some additional neat things that I don&#39;t know where to put so i made it into a permanent button. Oops!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-me&quot;&gt;About Me&lt;a data-pagefind-ignore href=&quot;#about-me&quot; class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; aria-label=&quot;Permalink to About Me&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;tooltip&quot;&gt;Permanent link&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now would be a good time to ask... what is a vilijur? That&#39;s me. Hello! I&#39;m vilijur, I make stuff in Blender, I enjoy Nintendo games, and I think fish are funny. I&#39;m acting all profreshional here but in actuality I&#39;m way more silly. So you&#39;ll probably see my silliness shine a bit here. Hopefully that isn&#39;t too much of an issue...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might be wondering &lt;strong&gt;why&lt;/strong&gt; the icon is of a goldfish with pink hair and an eyepatch? If you are, then I shall respond with another question: &lt;em&gt;Why not?&lt;/em&gt; I did buy a domain that ends in &lt;code&gt;.fish&lt;/code&gt; and I&#39;d be dammed not to incorporate it in some way. Also, it&#39;s a goldfish because I&#39;m a tad bit forgetful... just a tad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;blender&quot;&gt;Blender&lt;a data-pagefind-ignore href=&quot;#blender&quot; class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; aria-label=&quot;Permalink to Blender&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;tooltip&quot;&gt;Permanent link&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve made quite a lot of renders over the few years I&#39;ve been using Blender. I wouldn&#39;t say they&#39;re professional grade by any means, but I&#39;m pretty satisfied with what I&#39;ve managed to create so far. Currently, you can find my artwork &lt;a href=&quot;https://bsky.app/profile/vilijur.fish/feed/aaalamsgnhmcc&quot;&gt;on my Bluesky&lt;/a&gt;, though I am hoping to move them onto a platform I have control over eventually. They were originally on my Twitter account, buuuut... some things may have happened and I may no longer have any of the posts on there at all... oops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;goals&quot;&gt;Goals&lt;a data-pagefind-ignore href=&quot;#goals&quot; class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; aria-label=&quot;Permalink to Goals&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;tooltip&quot;&gt;Permanent link&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of writing this, the blog is currently in a very, very simple form. There&#39;s not much here, but I am planning to post stuff here somewhat regularly. Some things you can possibly expect include, but are not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Behind the scenes on a project (such as a render)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some neat trivia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development logs on a project I&#39;m working on, and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever I feel like talking about that day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After all, it is my blog. I could put anything I want on it... maybe I&#39;ll add more fish...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This would be the part where I&#39;d ask for feedback but I don&#39;t quite have that setup on here. I guess you can send me a message on one of the links at the bottom of every page. You&#39;re not obligated to, but you can! If you want! Assuming you don&#39;t already have an easier means to contact me directly!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

 			</content>
        </entry>
        
    
</feed>